developersummit.com 2018-06-29

# Saltmarch Media

####  Terms of Use

[www.saltmarch.com](http://saltmarch.com/) is owned and operated by Saltmarch Media Pvt Ltd, a company incorporated under the laws of India. Your use of the web site and services and tools are governed by the following terms and conditions ("Terms of Use") as applicable to the web site including the applicable policies which are incorporated herein by way of reference. If you transact on the web site, You shall be subject to the policies that are applicable to the web site for such transaction. By mere use of the web site, You shall be contracting with Saltmarch Media Pvt Ltd and these terms and conditions including the policies constitute your binding obligations, with Saltmarch Media Pvt Ltd. For the purpose of these Terms of Use, wherever the context so requires "You" or "User" shall mean any natural or legal person who has agreed to become a buyer on the web site by providing Registration Data while registering on the web site as Registered User using the computer systems. [www.saltmarch.com](http://saltmarch.com/) allows the User to surf the web site or making purchases without registering on the web site. The term "We", "Us", "Our" shall mean Saltmarch Media Pvt Limited When You use any of the services provided by Us through the web site, including but not limited to, (e.g. Product Reviews, Seller Reviews), You will be subject to the rules, guidelines, policies, terms, and conditions applicable to such service, and they shall be deemed to be incorporated into this Terms of Use and shall be considered as part and parcel of this Terms of Use. We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change, modify, add or remove portions of these Terms of Use, at any time without any prior written notice to you. It is your responsibility to review these Terms of Use periodically for updates / changes. Your continued use of the web site following the posting of changes will mean that you accept and agree to the revisions. As long as you comply with these Terms of Use, We grant you a personal, non-exclusive, non-transferable, limited privilege to enter and use the web site.

When You use any of the services provided by Us through the web site, including but not limited to, (e.g. Product Reviews, Seller Reviews), You will be subject to the rules, guidelines, policies, terms, and conditions applicable to such service, and they shall be deemed to be incorporated into this Terms of Use and shall be considered as part and parcel of this Terms of Use. We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change, modify, add or remove portions of these Terms of Use, at any time without any prior written notice to you. It is your responsibility to review these Terms of Use periodically for updates / changes. Your continued use of the web site following the posting of changes will mean that you accept and agree to the revisions. As long as you comply with these Terms of Use, We grant you a personal, non-exclusive, non-transferable, limited privilege to enter and use the web site.

ACCESSING, BROWSING OR OTHERWISE USING THE SITE INDICATES YOUR AGREEMENT TO ALL THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS UNDER THESE TERMS OF USE, SO PLEASE READ THE TERMS OF USE CAREFULLY BEFORE PROCEEDING.

#### Privacy Policy

##### SALTMARCH MEDIA (INDIA) PVT. LTD, PRIVACY POLICY

For us privacy for our valued customer is very important. We strongly believe that the personal information of our customers should not be shared with the third party without the prior consent or request from the customer. Privacy is the right of an individual and at Saltmarch Media Pvt Ltd the information of the customer such as contact no., email, addresses etc is used only for the internal purpose and not for sale. Your contact information is stored in our database and is only used to contact you during the course of your stay with us for sharing the status of your room bookings with us and then after for announcement of our latest deals and news etc. We at Saltmarch Media Pvt Ltd condemn the unauthorised reach and misuse and/or discloser of the personal information of the customer and we have strict guidelines and high security features to prevent the same. Any changes in our 'Privacy Policy' will be posted here on the web site.

##### INTRODUCTION

At Saltmarch Media (India) Private Ltd (hereinafter referred to as Saltmarch Media) we take your privacy rights, and your expectation of privacy, very seriously. This Privacy Policy describes Saltmarch Media's policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of your information which you provide when you use Saltmarch Media's web site www.saltmarch.com, Saltmarch Media's conference-related web sites and web sites hosted on any/all domains owned by Saltmarch Media (the "web sites"), when you use the related services and features offered on the web sites, and when you subscribe to or register for and attend Saltmarch Media's conferences and webinars (the web sites, the related services and features, including any of Saltmarch Media's mobile and digital applications, the conferences and webinars, and any other products and/or services offered by Saltmarch Media are collectively referred to as the "Saltmarch Media Products").

Your use of any of the Saltmarch Media Products to which this policy is linked confirms that you have read and accepted this Privacy Policy and the Terms & Conditions of Service applicable to the specific Saltmarch Media Product.

Saltmarch Media will not use or share your information obtained through your use of the Saltmarch Media Products for any purpose or with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy. However, please note that this Privacy Policy does not apply to information we collect by other means or from other sources.

 **HOW WE COLLECT YOUR INFORMATION**

 **Information You Provide.** When you access the web sites, subscribe to, register for or participate in conferences or webinars, use mobile or digital applications, participate in social networking, enter contests or surveys, make purchases of any Saltmarch Products, or at other times, we collect and store personally identifiable information (generally defined to mean information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact or locate a single person, or identify an individual in context) about you that may include, your name, postal and e-mail addresses, professional affiliation, information regarding your computer system, and other information.

We request certain information from you if you make a payment from our web site or third-party service provider sites. You must provide contact information, such as your e-mail address, and financial information, such as a credit/debit card number and the expiration date. Financial information is used for payment processing purposes only. We use a credit/debit card processing company to process credit/debit card charges for Saltmarch Media Products. We do not retain, share, store or use credit/debit card information for any secondary purposes (subject to central and state laws) and will exercise reasonable care to prevent disclosure or use of credit/debit card information.

 **Information Provided By Third Parties.** We may from time to time obtain information about you from third-parties such as business partners, database agencies, mobile carriers or other companies. If you use your login credentials from a social networking site ("SNS") to use an Saltmarch Media Product, we may receive information from such SNS in accordance with the terms and conditions of the SNS. We may use any information about you which we receive from a third party to include in our database(s) or append to existing user data to add more detail to the information we have about you.

 **Cookies.** For each visitor to our web sites, our web server may automatically attempt to identify the user through a cookie placed within the user's web browser (a cookie is a message given to a web browser by a web server; the browser stores the message in a text file; the message is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server). This is done to provide users with more relevant access to the web sites. From time to time we may also track information, in aggregate, on pages and features that users access or view. The activity is collected and stored in our server's log files. We may log Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, or the location of your computer on the Internet, for systems administration and troubleshooting purposes. We use this information in an aggregate fashion to track access to the web sites. Our email alerts utilize tracking technology that allows us to see how many newsletter e-mails are opened and the e-mail address of users who have clicked on a given post, feature or advertisement. We use this information for internal purposes, to measure the aggregate number of people who view a given newsletter item.

We may also place cookies on users' computers to allow users to store login information, personalize their user experience and navigate easily through the web sites. Through the use of additional cookies or technology, we will have the ability to track users by their behavior profile and geographic location for the purpose of pushing advertising that matches their interests and/or specific location. We may, and may enable our advertisers to, collect your location via certain services we provide through digital applications, wireless access protocol (WAP) services or mobile phone services. We, or the service provider, will inform you of such collection at the time you use the service. By using such service, you consent to our collection, use and disclosure of your location information as described.

 **Third Party Advertisements.** We may use third-party advertising service vendors to serve advertisements on Saltmarch Media Products. These vendors may use cookies, web beacons or similar technologies to serve you advertisements tailored to interests you have shown by browsing on this and other sites you have visited. In doing so, these vendors may collect non-personal data such as your browser type, your operating system, Web pages visited, time of visits, content viewed, ads viewed, and other clickstream data. The use of cookies, web beacons or similar technologies by these advertising service vendors is subject to their own privacy policies, not ours, and we disclaim all liability in connection therewith. 

**HOW WE USE AND SHARE YOUR INFORMATION**

Information collected about you may be used by us and our affiliates and partnering third-party companies to provide you with the features of the Saltmarch Media Products and with the products and services you requested, to personalize content and advertising, to send you e-mail notifications about our products and services, to perform statistical analysis of user behavior in order to measure interest in the various Saltmarch Media Products (such as for product development purposes), to enforce our user agreement, and to inform advertisers as to how many users have seen or "clicked" their advertising banners.

Saltmarch Media may share your personally identifiable information with third parties for the purpose of providing the Saltmarch Media Products to you or with third parties offering combined services with Saltmarch Media. Additionally, when you participate in Saltmarch Media conferences, webinars or other events, we may share information about you with event sponsors. If we do any of this, such third parties' use of your information will be bound by this Privacy Policy. If you prefer not to have your personal information disclosed to third-parties for direct marketing purposes, please send us e-mail us at privacy@saltmarch.com or call us at +91 80 4264 4264, stating this preference and providing your full name and e-mail address.

 **SECURE ONLINE PAYMENTS**

The visitor on our web site please take a note that your name, email address and other personal information submitted on our web site may be stored with us and may also appear on the web site. Like other platforms our server log files also receives general information such as IP address of the visitor, cookie etc. For the financial transactions by credit card Saltmarch Media Pvt Ltd uses a 3rd party secure payment gateway provided by "PayU" and the credit card details are 'not stored' with Saltmarch Media Pvt Ltd, instead the information is securely stored and encrypted with Visa/MasterCard.

 **Smart Cookies**

We use cookies to keep track of your current shopping session to personalize your experience and so that you may retrieve your shopping cart at any time. Cookies are tiny text files that our web site places on your computer's hard drive to store information about your shopping session and to identify your computer.

 **Return, Refund and Cancellation Policy**

We do not entertain return, refund and cancellation in any circumstances. In case of double or failed transactions and payment has been debited refund will be processed through same mode within a stipulated period of time.

 **OTHER DISCLOSURES OF YOUR INFORMATION**

We may store personal information in locations outside the direct control of Saltmarch Media (for instance, on servers or databases co-located with hosting providers or on the cloud).

As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or business offerings. Customer, email, phone and visitor information is generally one of the transferred business assets in these types of transactions. We may also transfer or assign such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or dissolution. In such cases we cannot control acquiring parties' use of your information.

We may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or if we believe that it is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation or legal request; to protect the safety of any person; to address fraud, security or technical issues; or to protect Saltmarch Media's rights or property.

 **YOUR RIGHT TO OPT OUT**

 **Opt-Outs.** You may request for deletion, modifications, corrections to your preferences or personal information at any time by writing to Database Manager, Saltmarch Media, 2A&B, Raintree Hall, Rhenius Street, Richmond Town, Bangalore, Karnataka, India, Pin code: 560025 or email privacy@saltmarch.com or call 91 80 4264 4264. We retain the right to contact you regarding account status, orders for products or services, changes to the registration agreement or to enforce our subscription agreement.

We will remove you (and your personal information) from our databases pursuant to your request, if you contact us as provided above. You may not be able to fully access a Saltmarch Media Product if your personal information is removed.

 **Mobile Consents/Opt-Outs.** We may provide you messages, including marketing, via your wireless email address or by short message service, wireless access protocol services or mobile phone service. By providing us with you wireless email address or by signing up for any SMS, WAP or mobile phone service, you consent to receive services and messages at the address or number you provide for such purposes, and understand that your wireless carrier's rates apply to these services/messages. You may opt-out of SMS, WAP or mobile services by sending an e-mail stating this preference and including your full name, mobile telephone number and e-mail address to privacy@saltmarch.com or call 91 80 4264 4264.

 **HOW WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place administrative controls to help protect the information. Please note that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while Saltmarch Media uses reasonable efforts to protect your personal information, it cannot guarantee its absolute security.

All credit/debit card payment and bank transfer instructions that you may have provided to avail of Saltmarch Media's Products through its partners, affiliates and/or third-party service providers, ticketing engines etc., is subject to the terms and conditions as published on the third-party providers web site. Saltmarch Media cannot guarantee security of such information.

In the event that personal information is compromised as a result of a breach of security, Saltmarch Media will promptly notify those persons whose personal information has been compromised, in accordance with the notification procedures set forth in this Privacy Policy, or as otherwise required by applicable law.

 **CHILDREN'S PRIVACY**

Protecting the privacy of children is especially important to us. Saltmarch Media does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to use the Saltmarch Media Products. If we become aware that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information.

 **LINKS TO OTHER WEB SITES**

Saltmarch Media Products may contain links to other web sites or services that may be subject to less stringent privacy standards. Saltmarch Media cannot assume any responsibility for the privacy practices, policies or actions of the third parties that operate these web sites or services. We are not responsible for how such third parties collect, use or disclose your personal information. You should review their privacy policies before providing them with personal information.

 **NON-INDIA USERS**

Saltmarch Media's web sites are operated in India. If you are located outside of India, please be aware that any information you provided to us will be transferred to India. By using Saltmarch Media's Products, participating in any of our services and/or providing us with your information, you consent to this transfer.

 **CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on this page to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page. Please check this page on a consistent basis.

 **QUESTIONS?**

If you have any questions about our practices or this privacy policy, please contact Database Manager, Saltmarch Media, 2A&B, Raintree Hall, Rhenius Street, Richmond Town, Bangalore, Karnataka, India, Pin code: 560025 or email privacy@saltmarch.com or by phone to +91 80 4264 4264.
